<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<products>
<asus><![CDATA[
<u>Asus Zenphone 6</u>
<br>
<img src="images/Asus-zenphone-6.jpg"/><br>
The Asus Zenfone 6 is the largest model in Asus new phone line-up – a set of phones out to establish Asus as a real phone brand. It gets you a 6-inch screen, and both a better processor and camera than the slightly smaller Zenfone 5.
We think the Zenfone 5 phone is pretty great, especially as it starts at just £150. The Zenfone 6 is a slightly tricker proposition as its size introduces a few usability issues, and it costs a fair bit more at £250 without 4G. But it’s ultimately a solid phone in almost every respect, and a good deal if you don’t mind about having a brand on the back your friends might turn their noses up at.
]]>
    </asus>
<lumia><![CDATA[
<u>MIcrosoft Lumia 535</u><br>
<img src="images/microsoft-lumia-535.jpg"/><br>
The Microsoft Lumia 535 doesn’t offer high-end specs, but it’s certainly a step up from the slightly older Lumia 530. Powered by a quad-core 1.2 GHz Snapdragon 200 processor, the phone features a 5-inch IPS display with 540 x 960 pixels, HSDPA, Wi-Fi 802.11 b/g/n, Bluetooth 4.0, 1 GB of RAM, 8 GB of expandable internal memory, and a 1905 mAh battery. On the back, the Lumia 535 has a 5 MP camera with LED flash, while its front-facing shooter is the same 5 MP one that we can find on the selfie-centric Lumia 730 / 735.
]]></lumia>
<yu><![CDATA[
<u>Micromax Yu Yureka</u>
<br>
<img src="images/micromax-yu-yureka.jpg"/><br>
Micromax Yureka (yes, it is not YU but YUREKA) has been launched and suprisingly the phone is priced below what most would have expected. At Rs. 8999/- the phone probably has one of the highest “Value For Money” quotient!
While most of the details we put up yesterday (read below) are bang on, we expected a 3GB RAM phone with higher storage space. But at Rs. 8999, there is nothing much to complain about. 
]]>
</yu>
<xaomi><![CDATA[
<u>Xaomi Redimi Note 4g </u><br>
<img src="images/xaomi-note-4g.jpg"/><br>
The Redmi Note have two versions: with an octa-core 1.4GHz CPU and 1GB of RAM, and with an octa-core 1.7Ghz CPU and 2GB of RAM. In both cases, the processor is a MediaTek MTK6592. Other (common) features include a MIUI interface on top of Android Jelly Bean, a 5.5 inch IPS display with 720 x 1280 pixels, dual SIM and dual stand-by capabilities, microSD card support, a 13MP rear camera with LED flash, and a 5MP front-facing camera. The handset comes with a 3,200 mAh battery that should provide enough juice even for hardcore users.
]]>
</xaomi>
</products>



